ILGWU. David Melman papers, 5780/152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 153: Jimmy Rivera, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Local 153: Negotiations, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Chris Starobin, 1989-1991 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Murray Ferguson, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Arnold and Porter, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Arnold and Porter, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Arnold and Porter, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 1 of 3], 1992 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 2 of 3], 1992 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 3 of 3], 1992 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 1 of 2], 1993 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 2 of 2], 1993 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 1 of 2], 1994 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Arnold and Porter [folder 2 of 2], 1994 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Arnold and Porter: Environmental Site Assessment, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  July 15
- Arnold and Porter, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Mode O'Day. 1979 Negotiations (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Summary of Agreement, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Summary of Agreement, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Financial Clippings, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Mode O'Day [folder 1 of 5], 1978-1985 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Mode O'Day [folder 2 of 5], 1978-1985 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Mode O'Day [folder 3 of 5], 1978-1985 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Mode O'Day [folder 4 of 5], 1978-1985 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Mode O'Day [folder 5 of 5], 1978-1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Kay Windsor, 1973-1982 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- The Barbizon Corporation, 1980-1983 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Upper South Department.1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Southeast Region. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Puerto Rico. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Northeast Department. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- New York State Region. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- New York City Locals. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- New Jersey Region. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- New England. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Midwest Region. 1989 Election Notices, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Official Election Returns, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- 1988-1989 Elections (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Canada. 1989 Election Notices (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Central States. 1989 Election Notices (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region. 1989 Election Notices (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Maidenform. Negotiations [folder 1 of 6], 1981-1984 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Maidenform. Negotiations [folder 2 of 6], 1981-1984 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Maidenform. Negotiations [folder 3 of 6], 1981-1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Maidenform. Negotiations [folder 4 of 6], 1981-1984 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Maidenform. Negotiations [folder 5 of 6], 1981-1984 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Maidenform. Negotiations [folder 6 of 6], 1981-1984 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Election Correspondences, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Election Notice Forms, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Two-Day Elections, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Election Forms, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Election Form Problems, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Completed Election Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Triangle Fire Essays, 1990-1991 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Triangle Fire Exhibit. Miscellaneous Articles, 1961-1987 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Gus Tyler Articles, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Tenement Museum Sweatshop Project Grant Proposal, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Lower East Side Tenement Museum Benefit Dinner, 6/8/1999 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Lower East Side Tenement Museum Book, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Triangle Fire Memorial Ceremony, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Triangle Fire Anniversary Forum, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Unite! Triangle Fire Commemoration, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Triangle Fire Memorial Plaque, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1997-1999 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Tailored Clothing Research Project, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Textile Industry and Unite!, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Textile Processors, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Trade and GATT, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Echo Repertory. The Triangle Project, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Triangle Fire Miscellaneous. High School Play, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Triangle Fire Plays, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- The New Stage Craft Company, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Triangle Fire Postage Stamp Proposal, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Triangle Fire New York Photographs (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Triangle Fire Slide Shows, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Triangle Fire. Leon Stein (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Triangle Fire. Leon Stein Audio Tape, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- The Sweatshop Project. Italian Scholars, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- The Sweatshop Project. Scholars Final Papers [folder 1 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- The Sweatshop Project. Scholars Final Papers [folder 2 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- The Sweatshop Project Correspondences, 1996-1998 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- The Sweatshop Project, 1995-1998 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Sweatshop Conferences, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- The Sweatshop Campaign, 1995-1997 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- Sweatshop Legislation. New York State, 1995-1997 (Box 60, Folder 32)
- "Pins and Needles", 1977-1992 (Box 60, Folder 33)
- Adopt-A-Mural Project. History of the Needlecraft Industry by the Fashion High School, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- Sweatshop Smithsonian Exhibit, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Fair Trade Federation, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- David Dubinsky. Labor Hall of Fame, 1991-1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- William Daniels. Personal, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Costume Industry, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Theatrical Costume Shops, 1993-1996 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Council for American Fashion, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Communication Workers of America, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Sol C. Chaikin Papers, 1983-1991 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Sol. C. Chaikin. Long Island Jewish Hospital, 1982-1991 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Benefit Fund Project, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Bund Research, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  Hebrew
- California Federation of Teachers, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Catherwood Library, 1997-1998 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- American Federation of Teachers, 1995-1997 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Arbitrator Biographies (Box 61, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- ACTWU Holding Company, Inc., 1996 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Services, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Apparel Industry Partnership, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Apparel Task Force, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Asia Pacific Labor Alliance, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Auto Industry, 1995-1996 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Jewish Museum, New York City [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1998 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Jewish Museum, New York City [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1998 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Major Market Negotiations, 1994-1997 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Contract Settlements, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Opt-Out, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Retired Staff Healthcare, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 29)
- Retired Staff Benefits, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Mission Statement, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 31)
- Mob Articles, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Mob-ILGWU History, 1979-1982 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- National Labor Committee, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 34)
- National Museum of American History, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 35)
- General Executive Board Minutes and Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Minutes and Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Meeting Minutes- June, 7, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board Regional Reports, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Department Reports, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Central States Merger Resolutions, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Upper South States Merger Resolutions, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board Meeting on Organizing, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Reports from Task Forces, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Resolutions and Minutes, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Minutes, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board Regional Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Regional Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board Department Reports, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Northeast Department, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board Meeting Notes, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Minutes- March, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board Meeting Decisions, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board Resolutions, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board Meeting 2/6-16/1978 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Meeting 2/6-16/1978 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Meeting 9/1-15/1978 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board Meeting 2/26-28/1979 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board Meeting 2/26-28/1979 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Meeting 1/5-8/1981 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board Meeting 1/5-8/1981 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board Meeting 8/20-22/1979 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board Meeting 8/20-22/1979 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 63, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Meetings, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Regional Reports, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Department Reports, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Meeting Agendas, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Campaign Committee, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Finances and Census, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Guests and Members, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Hotel Arrangements, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- International Affairs, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Irwin Solomon Report, 1988-1989 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Legal Issues, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board Minutes, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Union Health Center Committee Meeting, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Lou Montenegro, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Edgar Romney, 1956-1973 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Task Forces, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board Minutes and Attachments-May, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board Agenda, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board Minutes and Attachments-June, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Minutes and Attachments, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board Regional Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board Regional Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board Department Reports, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board Agenda, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- General Executive Board Minutes, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Irwin Solomon Report, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Resolutions, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Unity House, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Union Management Committees, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Organizations, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Comparable Worth, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 30A)
- Central America Trip-Joseph Fisher, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 30B)
- Legal Referral, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Garment Center Zoning Plan, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 32)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board Department Reports, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 34)
- General Executive Board Agenda, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Benefit Funds, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Campaign Committee Endorsements, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Homework, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Irwin's Report (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Local 153 Negotiations, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 40)
- Resolutions, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 41)
- General Executive Board Minutes, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Task Force Reports, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 43)
- Unity House, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Union Privilege Benefit Programs, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 45)
- Technology Changes in the Garment Industry, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 46)
- Union Privilege Legal Services, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 47)
- Agreement between Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers Inc. and ILGWU, 1978-1981 (Box 64, Folder 48)
- Resolutions and Committee Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Minutes, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Department Reports, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Regional Reports, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Settlement, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Education Task Force, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- General Advisory Council, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- GIAC, Mario Cuomo and New York City and State Affairs, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- International Affairs, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Irwin Solomon Report, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Task Force Reports, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Immigration, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Health Services Plan, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Campaign Committee Presidential Elections, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Trade Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- American Family Celebration Local Action Kit, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board Department Reports, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Regional Reports, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Task Force Reports, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board Minutes and Resolutions, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Campaign Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board Topics, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- ILG Fashion Show, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Homework, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Archives, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. Wilbur Daniels, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- IUD-UHC Sharing, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Levy Brothers (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Census, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 29)
- Report to the General Executive Board, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 30)
- Delegate Selection Process, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Immigration Act, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 32)
- Victor Gotbaum, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 33)
- Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Third Meeting of the General Executive Board, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 35)
- Drafts of General Executive Board Minutes, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 36)
- Resolution of the General Executive Board, Local 93 and Central Pennsylvania District Council, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 37)
- General Executive Board Resolutions and Minutes, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 38)
- General Executive Board. Hazelton and Wyoming Valley District Councils, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 39)
- General Executive Board. Philadelphia-South Jersey District Council, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 40)
- General Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 41)
- Irwin Solomon's Report, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 42)
- General Executive Board Minutes, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 43)
- Convention Decisions, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 44)
- Union Sanatorium Association, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 45)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 46)
- The Bali Company Protests, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 47)
- Guests to the General Executive Board, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 48)
- Cinnabar Lane, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 49)
- General Executive Board Discussion of Organizing, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 50)
- Donations, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 51)
- General Executive Board. Topics for Discussion, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 52)
- Census Comparison, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 53)
- General Executive Board and Homework, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 54)
- Leslie Fay Company Reports, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Inc. v. Corporate Property Associates 3, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Leslie Fay Corporate Campaign Congressional Hearings, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Leslie Fay Corporate Campaign Congressional Hearings, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Leslie Fay Contract Termination Notices, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Leslie Fay Miscellaneous Clippings [folder 1 of 3] (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Leslie Fay Miscellaneous Clippings [folder 2 of 3] (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Leslie Fay Miscellaneous Clippings [folder 3 of 3] (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Leslie Fay Clippings, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Leslie Fay Clippings, 1982-1986 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Leslie Fay. Theo Miles Correspondence, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Leslie Fay. Toronto Correspondence, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Leslie Fay Arbitration, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Leslie Fay Campaign Board of Directors, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Leslie Fay Summit Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Leslie Fay Spitalnick Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1992 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Leslie Fay Spitalnick Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1992 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Leslie Fay Sportswear Correspondence, 1982-1994 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Leslie Fay Correspondence, 1983-1993 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Leslie Fay Shapely Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Leslie Fay Correspondences, 1983-1987 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Leslie Fay Restivo Correspondence, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Leslie Fay Severance Pay Correspondence, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Leslie Fay Pennsylvania Grievance, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Head Sportswear Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Leslie Fay Hue Correspondence, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Leslie Fay Jorca Correspondence, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Julia I and Julia II Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Leslie Fay Next Day Apparel Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Leslie Fay Albert Nippon Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Leslie Fay Outlander Correspondence, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Leslie Fay Overton Apparel Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Leslie Fay Evelyn Pearson Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Leslie Fay Breckenridge Correspondence, 1982-1993 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Leslie Fay Wilbur Daniels Correspondence, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- AmeriMex Articles, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Ames Benefits (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Ames Contracts. Chicago Agreement, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Ames Contracts. Florida Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Ames Contracts. Georgia Agreement, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Ames Contracts. Secaucus Agreement, 1986-1992 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Ames Contracts. Pennsylvania Agreement, 1990-1994 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Zayres/Ames, 1988-1991 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Ames Miscellaneous, 1988-1994 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Biflix, 1987-1990 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Cattiva, Inc., 1995 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Coat Industry, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Bobbie Brooks Correspondence, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Cornish Knitgoods, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Brian Uzzi, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Casablanca Group L.P. (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Crystal Brands Company and Audit Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Crystal Brands Company and Audit Reports, 1985-1992 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Crystal Brands Correspondence, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Crystal Brands Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Crystal Brands Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Crystal Brands. 40 Hour Week, 1987-1991 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Crystal Brands Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Crystal Brands. Aston, PA Agreements, 1987-1990 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Crystal Brands and Eaglewear, Inc., 1982-1990 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Crystal Brands. Evan Picone Contracts, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Crystal Brands. Evan Picone Contracts, 1988-1990 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Crystal Brands Agreements [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1989 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- Crystal Brands Agreements [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1989 (Box 68, Folder 29)
- Crystal Brands Financial Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Crystal Brands, Inc. and ILGWU Local 93, 1990-1993 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Crystal Brands Negotiations, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Crystal Brands. Jane and Linda Sportswear, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Crystal Brands with Local 93, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Crystal Brands Letter Agreements, 1983-1988 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Crystal Brands Original Signed Copies, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Crystal Brands NYC Jobbers Agreement, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Crystal Brands. Ashton, PA Draft, 1987-1990 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Crystal Brands. Baxley, GA Drafts, 1987-1990 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Crystal Brands. Reading, PA Draft, 1987-1990 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Crystal Brands Draft of Master Agreement, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Crystal Brands Master Drafts- First Version, 1987-1990 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Crystal Brands and Evan Picone Division, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Jones Apparel Group, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Crystal Brands [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1993 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Crystal Brands [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1993 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Dawson Home Fashions, 1992-1994 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Dawson Home Fashions. Sardis, Mississippi Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Dawson Home Fashions Vienna, Ohio Agreement Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- Crystal Brands Corporate Campaign, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement Back-Up File, 1991-1994 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Calvin Klein Bills, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Calvin Klein Bills, 1987-1989 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Calvin Klein 1989 Bill, 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Calvin Klein 1990 Bill, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Calvin Klein 1991 Bill, 1991-1993 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Calvin Klein 1992 Bill, 1992-1994 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Calvin Klein 1993 Bill, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Calvin Klein 1994 Bill, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Calvin Klein 1995 Bill, 1995-1998 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Calvin Klein 1996 Bill, 1996-1998 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Calvin Klein Chart, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Calvin Klein Clippings, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Calvin Klein Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Calvin Klein Clippings, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Calvin Klein Clippings, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Calvin Klein Clippings, 1980-1994 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Calvin Klein Negotiations, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Calvin Klein Contract Termination Notices, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Calvin Klein Termination Notices, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Calvin Klein and Kaijay Contract, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Kaijay Correspondence, 1982-1994 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Calvin Klein 1991 Chart (Box 70, Folder 24)
- Calvin Klein Knitwear, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreements, 1988-1990 (Box 70, Folder 26)
- Calvin Klein Home, Inc., 1996 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- Calvin Klein NY Cutting and Samplemaking Supplemental Agreement, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 29)
- Calvin Klein North Bergen, NJ Warehouse Supplemental Agreement, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 30)
- Calvin Klein Original Signed Agreement, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 31)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 32)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1995 (Box 70, Folder 34)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1992-1994 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1992-1994 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Moody Corporation, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 3)